<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Concepts on The Things Stack for LoRaWAN Documentation</title>
    <link>https://thethingsstack.io/v3.1.2/concepts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Concepts on The Things Stack for LoRaWAN Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thethingsstack.io/v3.1.2/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>End Device Templates</title>
      <link>https://thethingsstack.io/v3.1.2/concepts/end-device-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thethingsstack.io/v3.1.2/concepts/end-device-templates/</guid>
      <description>What is it? End device templates define a device that is not created (yet). It can be used to create a device or many devices at once. Templates allows for using common values for many devices, such as a device profile.
Who is it for? End device templates are primarily targeted at device makers and service providers who are managing and onboarding large amounts of devices.
Typical use cases  Create a batch of end devices with the same profile and incrementing DevEUI from a range Convert vendor-specific end device data, such as serial numbers and provisioning data, to a device template Migrate end devices from a different LoRaWAN server stack  How does it work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Templates</title>
      <link>https://thethingsstack.io/v3.1.2/concepts/email-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thethingsstack.io/v3.1.2/concepts/email-templates/</guid>
      <description>What is it? Email templates define the contents of the emails that The Things Stack sends to its users. They allow network operators to override the default contents of the emails with their own custom contents.
Who is it for? Email templates are targeted at network operators that would like to customize the emails that The Things Stack sends to its users.
Typical use cases  Adding additional styling to the default text-only emails that The Things Stack sends.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>